playgamesnet.com 2018-05-14

# Privacy Policy

The privacy of our visitors is of extreme importance to FreePlayNow. This privacy policy document outlines the types of personal information is received and collected by FreePlayNow and how it is used. 

**Log Files**  
Like many other Web sites, FreePlayNow makes use of log files. The information inside the log files includes internet protocol ( IP ) addresses, type of browser, Internet Service Provider ( ISP ), date/time stamp, referring/exit pages, and number of clicks to analyze trends, administer the site, track user's movement around the site, and gather demographic information. IP addresses, and other such information are not linked to any information that is personally identifiable. 

**Cookies and Web Beacons**  
FreePlayNow use cookies to give you the best experience on our website. 

Some of our advertising partners may use cookies and web beacons on our site. Our advertising partners include  
CPMStar.com and GTBurst.com

These third-party ad servers or ad networks use technology to the advertisements and links that appear on FreePlayNow send directly to your browsers. They automatically receive your IP address when this occurs. Other technologies ( such as cookies, JavaScript, or Web Beacons ) may also be used by the third-party ad networks to measure the effectiveness of their advertisements and / or to personalize the advertising content that you see. 

FreePlayNow has no access to or control over these cookies that are used by third-party advertisers. 

You should consult the respective privacy policies of these third-party ad servers for more detailed information on their practices as well as for instructions about how to opt-out of certain practices. FreePlayNow's privacy policy does not apply to, and we cannot control the activities of, such other advertisers or web sites. 

We are committed to conducting our business in accordance with these principles in order to ensure that the confidentiality of personal information is protected and maintained. FreePlayNow may change this privacy policy from time to time at FreePlayNow's sole discretion.
